This has been by far the biggest AI news
week of 2025. Like, no questions. In
fact, this is the third video this week
where OpenAI is taking center stage. And
I can't start this video off without
first talking about Chat GPT5. This is
the newest, most state-of-the-art model
that blows away every single benchmark
that's out there. It's amazing at
coding. It's better at writing. It's
faster. You can make it think for longer
or shorter. It's definitely the best
version of Chat GPT we've gotten so far
and most likely the best model
available, period. Now, I did an entire
breakdown on August 7th, the day that
GPT5 came out and broke down everything
they announced in their keynote. Did a
little bit of testing with it and shared
my final thoughts about the keynote and
the launch. So, I'm not going to go too
deep, but I will give you the quick
TLDDR of everything they announced
around GBT5. They claim this new model
has EHD level intelligence on pretty
much every topic. It pretty much crushes
every single benchmark with the
competition math actually scoring 100%
when GPT5 had access to tools. Beats out
all the other models on math, science
questions, humanity's last exam, and
it's currently the best coding model. It
also supposedly hallucinates a heck of a
lot less and is less likely to deceive
you, which is, you know, important. One
thing you'll notice about the new model
is that, well, it's less confusing. If
you remember, the old model had this
drop down with all sorts of options of
models to choose from. Well, GPT5
doesn't make you think about which model
to pick. It's just got GPT5 and it has
some other models here, but I believe
these are only on the pro plan. So, for
the most part, you're just seeing GPT5
and no other models to use. It decides
based on your prompt whether it should
think more, think less, and how to
attack the prompt that you gave it. It's
also seemingly really fast. You can give
it a prompt, and it responds fairly
quickly, and it's being made available
for free users, plus users, pro users.
Everybody's getting access to this new
GPT5 model with the higher tier just
getting more prompts and more access to
it. GPT5 is starting to roll out today,
which is August 7th. So, by the time
you're seeing this, it should be
available to you to All Plus, Pro, Team,
and free users, and if you're enterprise
or an EDU customer, it's coming in a
week. You could custom tailor the
personality to make it more sarcastic,
more professional. There's going to be
four initial options, a cynic, a robot,
a listener, and a nerd. And it's also
available immediately for developers
inside the API which means that right
away as of today you can access it
inside of Windsurf Cursor Bolt any of
the AI coding tools it's available in.
And if for whatever reason you still
don't have this model rolled out into
your account. You're still seeing the
old version. It's already been rolled
out into Microsoft's Copilot. So you can
use it right now inside of Copilot. In
fact, if you head on over to
copilot.microsoft.com,
you get the chat here and under the
dropdown, you can see that I've already
got GPT5 available as an option. So, you
can chat with it today using Copilot if
it's not in your account for whatever
reason. I actually got it to make this
vampire survivors clone for me with just
one prompt, and it's actually really
good. I've got this character that
automatically shoots towards the
enemies. The enemies drop XP. I can
collect the XP. More and more waves of
enemies keep on coming as I keep
playing, including harder enemies that
look slightly different. And it even
added in these levelups that work really
well. I can click on this one and you
can see it added in a new weapon for my
character to use against the bad guys.
Like one shot, one prompt and it built
this. It's really, really impressive
when it comes to coding and is now the
new state-of-the-art coding model.
Again, I did an entire breakdown of
everything, a super deep dive into GPT5
on the day that it was announced. So, if
you want to go even deeper into what
GPT5 can do, make sure you check out
that video. But, you should have access
to chat GPT5 right now with these kinds
of capabilities. And it's pretty
mind-blowing. It seems to me that all of
these large language model companies,
Google, Anthropic, OpenAI, they've all
realized that the sort of killer use
case for these large language models is
coding because a you can quickly make
these bespoke apps just when you need
them for the exact thing that you need
them for. But b, if it can't figure out
how to solve a problem with the training
that's already within its vector
database, well, it can write a script
and use code to then solve the problem.
And it seems like all of the companies
are going in this direction because
again, if the next word prediction
doesn't solve the problem for you, well,
creating a little app that then chat GPT
runs on your behalf could theoretically
solve the problem that the next word
prediction couldn't solve, opening up
all sorts of possibilities as these
things get better and better at coding.
And that was just one of two big
releases that OpenAI had this week. They
also introduced GPTOSS, which is their
open weight models. They released two
models, GPTO OSS 120B and GPTOSS 20B.
These are models that can actually be
run locally or in the cloud and they
share no data back to OpenAI or the
company you're using them with because
they're these open weights locally run
models. And they're really powerful.
They're about as powerful as the last
generation of models that we got before
GPT5. They released this a couple days
early and said, "Look, this is an
openweight model. Do whatever you want
with it. go build off it, iterate it,
fine-tune it, do whatever you want with
this model. It's as good as all of the
models we've put out so far. And then
two days later, they released GPT5,
which is now the state-of-the-art best
model. But this GPT OSS is like as good
as the best models before GPT5, just
made available open weights. So, just to
sort of solidify this point and beat
this dead horse a little bit more, this
is a model that OpenAI released for you
use completely free. You don't need
internet to use it once you have it
downloaded. It doesn't send any data
anywhere because you could run it
offline and locally. And it's as good as
the state-of-the-art models up until
earlier this week. And this is one where
I also made an entire breakdown video on
the day it came out, including a
complete tutorial on how you can
download it and run it locally using LM
Studio. So, if you want to know more
about this model, what it's capable of,
and actually learn how to install it and
run it yourself, 100% free, make sure
you check out the video I put out all
about GPTO OSS from earlier this week. I
was recently accused of being an OpenAI
shill, but to be honest, I go where the
news is and I talk about where the
biggest most important news is
happening. And this week, it has been
completely OpenAI. And I mean, in lesser
OpenAI news, I should probably mention
this. They put out this blog post called
what we're optimizing chat GPT for and
they mentioned that they're worried
about people's mental health from using
chat GPT too much. So you could in the
near future actually get a quick popup
while using chat GPT that says this just
checking in. You've been chatting a
while. Is this a good time for a break?
And kind of suggest like, dude, chill
out. You've been in here for too much.
Go touch grass.
We also got a big launch out of
Enthropic this week. They released
Claude Opus 4.1.
Claude Opus 4.1 was the most powerful,
best performing AI coding model on the
planet for about 24 hours and then of
course GPT5 came and totally
overshadowed it. Now, I haven't done a
whole lot of sideby-side comparison, and
I imagine we'll be testing it more, and
there'll be a lot of other channels sort
of comparing them to see how well 4.1
does against GPT5, especially in coding
tasks, but I haven't gone that deep yet.
But this new Claude Opus 4.1 model was
totally optimized and designed to be a
better coding model. We can see Opus 4.1
scored a 74.5%
on the Swebench verified which ranks how
good it is at software development. And
again, this was the best we've seen out
of any coding model. That is, of course,
until GPT5 came along and beat it with a
74.9%.
When it comes to the actual API, Claude
Opus 4.1 is quite a bit more expensive
than the new GPT5 as well. $15 per
million input tokens and $75 per million
output tokens. G GPT5 in comparison is
$1.25 per million input tokens and $10
per million output tokens. So I mean not
even in the same ballpark even though
GPT5 is slightly better now. But if I
head on over to claude.ai, I can
actually access the Cloud 4.1 Opus model
as one of my options here. So, let's go
ahead and select that and let's give it
a quick test prompt and see how it codes
something up for us real quick. I'm
going to give it this prompt here. Go
ahead and pause it if you want to see
the full prompt, but essentially I'm
asking it to make a fitness app that
guides me through a 30 minute workout
and targets different muscle groups and
has countdown timers and things like
that. Let's see if it can get all of
this into a single app here. I will say
Claude 4.1 while it's actually writing
the code feels slightly faster than GPT5
to me, but I haven't put them side
byside yet. And we can see here's what
it spit out. We got this personal
trainer 30 minute daily workout. Key
features, seven different 30inut workout
routines. Each targets different muscle
groups. They're all body weight only. No
equipment needed. Smart timers, audio
feedback, progress tracking, achievement
system, motivation, modern design. I
mean, yeah, it did a pretty good job.
Let let's make this a little bit wider
here and click start workout. Okay, so
we got audio feedback. We are getting
some sound. Uh we are getting an
exercise timer. I could pause my timer,
resume my timer. It's wanting me to do
squats followed by jump squats. I want
to see what happens when the timer runs
down here. So once it hits zero, telling
me to take a 20 second break. Once this
countdown gets towards the end here, now
it's going to the jump squats. And we
can see next up is going to be lunges.
So it's working me through this workout.
I'm guessing if I did it on a different
day, it would give me a different set of
workouts. Pretty damn good for one
prompt if I'm being honest. Just out of
curiosity, I tossed the identical prompt
into chat GBT5. It wrote a heck of a lot
less code. This is a way smaller code
file here than what Claude wrote, but
let's run the code and see what happens.
All right, much simpler website out of
GPT5. Daily 30 minute workout. Press
start. Let's see what happens. All
right. So, jumping jacks with a 30-se
secondond countdown. And when the
countdown runs down to zero here, we get
a little rest. 10 seconds it looks like.
And then moves on to push-ups. No
audible feedback. We're not getting the
sounds. We don't have the sort of
tracking and the visual dashboard that
we got. So, Opus actually did a better
job on one prompt out of the gate with
this. So, I think a lot of people are
going to debate whether they prefer GPT5
versus Opus 4.1 when it comes to coding.
They both seem to work really, really
well. Opus 4.1 did this one better on
the first prompt, though. As someone
who's not loyal at all to any one model,
I think it's going to be really fun to
sort of jump back and forth. And if GPT5
gets hung up on a coding problem that it
can't seem to solve, well, jump over to
Opus 4.1 and see if it will solve it.
It'll be a lot more expensive with their
API, but maybe it'll solve a problem
that GPT5 couldn't. And vice versa, and
you could switch back and forth to
whatever one works the best. And if you
want a really inexpensive coding model,
you use Gemini 2.5, which is probably
the best economical pricing model. I
just love the fact that we have all of
these options, and all of them are so
good. Now, we also got some news out of
Nvidia recently. They launched their
version 4.0 with the new AI Twin
feature. This feature allows you to
upload videos of yourself and create a
digital clone of yourself or use one of
the pre-created avatars that they've
already got. So, check this out. If I
log into my Nvidia account here and I
click on create AI video, there's a new
button here that says AI twins. I have
the option to create a twin from
YouTube, record fresh, or clone just my
voice. So, for this video, let's record
from scratch and create a fresh new
avatar. I'll click on recording to
avatar. It tells me to upload at least
60 seconds of video and to make sure I
give Invidia AI permission with my words
in that video. So, I'm going to go ahead
and record that real quick and then
we'll go ahead and upload it and see
what happens. And now that I have my AI
avatar, I can go in and generate a
video. So, I can give it a prompt like
three grrowy facts that will blow your
mind in 30 seconds. Select my AI twin
here. We'll click continue. And now I
can generate my video. Think gravity is
pulling you down right now? Plot twist.
You're actually accelerating upward
through spaceime. Here's what else will
blow your mind about gravity. If you
fell into a black hole, time would slow
down so much that billions of years
would pass in the outside universe
before you even cross the event horizon.
Honestly, Nvidia's pretty great for
lastminute re-shoots, creating simple
and fun ads, or just messing around cuz
sometimes that's fun, too. And you can
actually try this AI avatar feature for
free over at invido.io,
I will make sure it is linked up in the
description. And thank you so much to
Nvidia for sponsoring today's episode.
Now, let's get back to it. And if just
the few things I've already mentioned
weren't enough to make this like the
biggest week ever, we got news out of
Google DeepMind as well. They showed off
their new Genie 3, which is a front tier
world model. And the Genie 3 website has
all sorts of other demos. Like this is
navigating maybe the surface of the moon
uh or navigating the surface of a
volcano. Here's one where somebody's
like on a jet ski during a festival of
lights navigating. And you can actually
see it just hit that light and the light
bumped off to the side as it hit it.
Walking on a pavement in Florida next to
a two-lane road. And there's waves
crashing over the side here. And the
user is able to look around in real time
as this is happening, tracking a
jellyfish underwater, flying a
helicopter around over a coastal cliff.
They're actually controlling this
helicopter and where it's pointing using
their arrow keys. This is just wild. And
there's a whole bunch of other demos on
their website that you can take a peek
at to see what this is really really
capable of because this this is honestly
just absolutely wild. Now, we don't have
access to actually play with this
ourselves yet. They're making it
available to early testers. I might be
able to get my hands on an early test to
play around with it, but this is
absolutely wild that this is all being
generated. Every single frame you're
seeing is being generated as the
character, the player uses the arrow
keys to move around on the level. Like,
they even jumped into this like flying
island. Wild stuff. A lot more demos
here. I won't spoil them. Check out the
Genie site. All links will be available
in the description. But mind blown what
you can do with this stuff already. Just
as somebody who's followed along to AI
for the last fiveish years, I am just so
blown away by what people are already
taking for granted. Like 5 years ago,
none of this was even close to possible.
I don't even think people were thinking
about making this kind of stuff 5 years
ago. And here we are already better than
I can even imagine. Jacob Bower here on
X showing another use case where you can
actually give it a video. This was a
video generated with VO3 and halfway
through the video it switched to Genie 3
and now he's controlling the flight. So
you can actually feed it videos and then
take control of the video. I mean, are
we not entertained? Google also rolled
out a feature this week that allows you
to create personal illustrated story
books using the Gemini app. And I
haven't tried it yet. So let's see what
it does. Try it today in the Gemini app.
So when I click the link, we can see
that it's on storybook here. Let's see
how creative it makes the story book if
I actually don't give it much details.
Create a story book with custom art that
tells a story about a young boy going on
an adventure. Everything about the
adventure is up to you, but should be
original and unique. Let's see what
story it generates for us, just not
giving it much to work with. So, it
immediately follows up with some more
details. Reader's age, let's go ahead
and say 10 years old. Illustration
style, let's do cartoon. And then tone.
Let's do humorous. And let it do its
thing. It took maybe a minute and a
half, but we've got our book here called
Sam's Epic Sock Adventure. So, we've got
our cover here. I guess that's Sam.
Pretty decent art. Sam, a boy with a map
in one hand and a flashlight in the
other. Stood at the top of the basement
stairs. Today, Sebastian, he declared to
his unimpressed cat. We venture into the
treacherous laundry room cavern to find
the lost socks of legend. Looks like the
whole thing's 10 pages. Here's page two.
I'm not going to read the whole thing,
but feel free to pause on any page if
you feel like reading the whole book.
Page three here. I mean, the art is all
very consistent as well, which is pretty
impressive. The character looks the
same. What's going on with that dry air
over there? Page six, page seven, page
eight, page nine, and finally, the kid
gets his socks. And we've got a button
that says start over. I mean, pretty fun
little app. I mean, it would be cool to
make little books for your kids. I'm
curious if it can make more of like an
adult book, too. Not what you're
thinking. You know, the book Go the F to
Sleep that people give new parents is
like a funny gift book. I wonder if it
can generate that kind of thing. So, I'm
going to go back to our little story
book gem here, and I am going to censor
this a little bit. This is a
family-friendly channel, but create a
story book called Put Your Away.
That's about a father who is constantly
picking up after his children. Is it
going to make it for us? Let's find out.
One thing to note is this time it didn't
ask follow-up instructions. It seemed to
know its task here. I'm actually kind of
shocked that it did it. We've got our
book here and our cover with our title.
Sorry, I'm censoring it, but you know
what it's about. Dad was a patient man,
a kind man, a man who loved his children
more than anything. But if he had to
pick up one more goddamn toy, he was
going to lose his mind. All right. All
looking good. Similar art style. Page
four. I mean, the art's all really good.
It all has a very consistent design.
Everything's looking great here. Page
seven, can find their toy. Page eight,
Leo and Mia looked at the mess. Then
they looked at the empty toy bins. Then
they looked at each other. The tiny
light bulb went on. Slowly, they started
to put their away. I mean, for the
most part, other than the title, and
then maybe two swear words in the entire
book. It's fairly friendly. It wasn't
quite as uh swear as the go the F to
sleep book, but I'm actually shocked
that it even allowed me to do this in
the first place. I thought it was going
to get denied. Grock rolled out a new
feature called Grock Imagine which can
create images and video. And when it
does create video, the video even has
audio similar to VO3. And it's really,
really fast. Now, at the moment, you
have to use it inside of the Gro app.
And it does say here it's now live to
all Super Grock and Premium Plus
subscribers. on the paid plans. However,
Elon Musk took the X to say for the next
few days, Grock Imagine Video Generation
is free to all US users. Download the
Gro app to try it out. So, you can
actually use it for free on the Gro app
if you're in the US. Now, what if you're
not in the US? Well, somebody went to X
to say, "Bro, just make it free for all
users worldwide." And well, Elon said,
"Use a VPN." So, apparently, if you're
using a VPN and you're outside the US,
you can make Grock Imagine work. So,
let's take a peek at it on the iPhone
here. So, inside the Gro app, you can
see at the very top there's an imagine
button. Also, down at the bottom there's
a create videos button. Let's just go
ahead and click on imagine at the top.
And you can see that there's a whole
bunch of images here that other people
have generated. And one of the easiest
things you can do to animate something
right out of the gate is just to pick an
image that's already been created. And
you can see there's a button that says
make video. Now, make sure when you use
this make video that uh you pick an
option. There's normal, fun, spicy, and
custom. And spicy mode, well, it's not
safe for work. Here's what happens when
I just do like fun mode on this Lego
Mona Lisa here. It starts to sort of
animate. There is audio, but it's not
playing through my computer, so I'm
holding my mic up. Hopefully, you can
hear that. It's a little weird. It did,
however, make three other generations
that you can pick between to see which
one you like, but they're all kind of
very similar and weird with this
specific video. Most of the videos I've
done don't come out this funky. If I
open up this mermaid one that somebody
made. Let's see what happens if I make
it spicy. I'll probably have to censor
this. So, that wasn't too bad. That
wasn't as spicy as some of the other
videos I made. You can see though that
I've done some of my normal tests.
Monkey on roller skates, Wolf Howling at
the Moon, it did pretty decent. But the
first time I ever did spicy mode out of
curiosity, it did this, which I don't
even think I can show you. So yeah, it
will it will do what you think it will
coming from an app made by Elon Musk. We
got a new image model called Quinn image
this week, which a lot of people are
claiming is the best image model out
there right now. It can do text. It can
do realistic images. It can do cartoon
images. People are just raving about
this. You can play with it by going over
to chat.quinn.ai
and clicking on the image generation
model here. And I can generate an image
like a wolf howling at the moon with
some text seen on the moon. And it
pretty much nails it. And I'm not even
logged in over here on Quinn. This let
me just generate it for free on their
website. I'm sure I'll run out of
generations at some point and they'll
want me to log in. But as of right now,
I generated this image not even needing
to be logged in. And the text is all
pretty good now. I mean, compared to
where we were a year and a half ago with
getting texted images, it's crazy. It's
just like a given now that an image
model will be able to do good text.
Speaking of image models, there's a new
model out of Leonardo, a company that I
do advise for. So, I want to just
disclaim that real quick, but it's
probably my favorite model of the moment
as when it comes to like models that
appeal to my visual aesthetic sense.
Like, I really like this new Lucid
Origin model and the images that it
makes. It reminds me of what we were
getting out of MidJourney back when
Midjourney V4 came out and everybody was
really really impressed. Like I really
like the aesthetics that we're getting
out of this. So if I'm in my Leonardo
account and I click on image here up on
my models, I can select Lucid Origin
here. I'm going to give it a prompt of a
vampire fighting a werewolf. Let's have
it improve my prompt for me real quick.
And let's generate that. And we can see
it made a very sort of painterly looking
image for each of these, which isn't
bad. That's not really the aesthetic
that I like to go for. So, let's
generate a new variation of the prompt
here. And we get some very cool like
comicbooky looking art here that I
really like the aesthetic of. Here's
some more that I generated. This one
almost looks like a game cutscene or
something. This one you got like some
realism going on. So, another really
good image model. And another feature
that Leonardo just rolled out is with
V3. If I click into the video mode, now
you can actually use VO3 and start with
an image for your video. This is brand
new. You weren't able to do a starting
frame. Before it was only text to video.
Now you can do image to video. So I can
click here to add a start frame. And I
can pick from images that I've already
uploaded here or I can pick from my
generations. So let's pick one of these
werewolf generations. Confirm it. give
it a basic prompt of a vampire fighting
a werewolf and let's see what we get out
of it. And here's what it generated. I
mean, it kind of feels like a fight in
slow motion and the vampire is teasing
the werewolf to eat his arm. But it's
really cool that Leonardo has image to
video generation now. And yes, I'm still
going with more crazy releases this
week. 11 Labs released a new feature
where now you can generate music from 11
Labs. you were already able to do text
to audio, uh, existing speech to a
different voice, sound effects, drum
machines. Now they're competing with SNO
and Udio. And you can generate full-on
music directly inside of 11 Labs. So,
let's jump into 11 Labs and try this
oursel. I have not generated music, so
this is going to be my first time
hearing it. Inside 11 Labs, I can see in
the left sidebar, we have music. And
right in the homepage, we also have
music. So, let's click into the music
section. And it says, "Describe your
song." Um, we can also describe the
duration. We'll leave it on auto. It
looks like it will generate two
variations of our song. I'll give it the
prompted early 2000s pop punk anthem
with three-part harmonies about how you
should watch Matt Wolf on YouTube to
keep looped in on the latest AI news. If
you've watched my channel for a while
now, you'll know that I'm a fan of early
2000's pop punk music. And when I've
tested Suno and Yo and tools like that
in the past, that's the style I generate
because I want to see how they compare.
So, let's see what it does. It's
interesting because it generated all the
lyrics right away. And then down at the
bottom, we can see like a timeline. And
as we watch it, you'll actually see new
audio get generated down here in the
timeline. So, verse three hasn't been
generated yet, but it's generated all
the way up through the chorus. Just kind
of cool to watch this generate in real
time in front of you. All right, so
let's take a quick listen to the song.
He's the ultimate scoop. Crank the
volume up. Get your brain on track. Join
the re.
Not bad at all. Now, personally, I still
think maybe Suno and Yuio do a slightly
better job, especially with the vocals.
You can still kind of hear that the
vocals are AI and the words sound a
little bit weird, like they blend words
together a little too much, but it
sounds good. I mean, I was bobbing my
head to the song. I feel like Sunno
still makes catchier songs out of the
gate, but again, this was the first
prompt, so there's probably a lot more I
can do to really fine-tune this and dial
it in. I will play with it a lot more.
Out of the gate, though, I don't
necessarily think it beats Suno, but
it's it's really good and it's really
fun to watch it generate in real time. I
do want to do one more quick test. I'm
going to click on music again and I want
to try to generate something without
vocals because you can actually create
like stems like just a baseline or just
a guitar rhythm or just vocals without
background music things like that. So
let's try a blues rhythm with just
rhythm guitar bass and drums, no vocals
and no lead guitar. It should be in the
key of G. Let's see what it generates
for us. is the idea being you can
generate like a rhythm backing track. If
I get something that's guitar, bass, and
drums, no singing, no lead guitar. Well,
then I can like jam over the top of it
with my real guitar if I wanted. We can
see up at the top include styles, blues,
rhythmic groove, instrumental, shuffle,
key of G, exclude styles, vocals, lead
guitar, solos, harmonica, keyboards. And
this is what it did. Okay, one second. I
got to tune it real quick.
[Music]
All right. So, super super fun,
especially if you're a musician and you
want to, you know, create other little
parts of the song and then overlay your
own instrumental or jam to a song that
AI made with you. Super super fun.
Really excited about that. And that was
the last demo that I wanted to share
today. There are a few other little
super quick things I wanted to share.
So, let's jump into a rapid fire
section.
If you're a big fan of using MidJourney,
they just rolled out an HD video mode if
you're one of the pro or mega
subscribers. So, you got to be on one of
their higherend paid plans. It is a
little bit more expensive to generate,
and by a little bit, quite a bit more.
3.2x more expensive, but you get four
times as many pixels than the default SD
video. So, if uh you need higherend
video coming out of MidJourney, well,
it's now available if you're on one of
those plans. The Google company Kaggle
is basically making a bunch of games
that they're going to use to test
different AI models against each other.
And the first thing they're doing is an
AI chess tournament to evaluate which
models are currently the best at chess.
It's a three-day long AI chess battle,
and it's the first in a series of
tournaments hosted by Google to find out
which model's the best at games. The
models will compete against each other
in a range of strategic games designed
to evaluate their thinking and reasoning
capabilities. For the first round,
they've partnered with chess.com,
so pretty soon we'll know which of the
available AI models is best at chess.
And then after chess, they're going to
put it up against a bunch of other
games. So, should be fun to watch and
follow along to. And finally, Elon Musk
went to X to say that Gro 5 will be out
before the end of the year and will be
crushingly good. And he made this post
on the same day that GPT5 launched. And
if I'm going to be honest, it feels a
little bit like there was a big news out
of OpenAI this week, big news out of
Google this week, uh fairly decentsized
news out of Anthropic this week, and X
was a little bit left out. Now, they did
put out imagine, but it doesn't feel
like as many people are talking about
it. And so Elon kind of went, well,
Grock 5 is coming and it's going to be
really, really good. That's kind of how
I feel about this tweet here. It's
probably not really the motives. I could
be reading way too much into this, but
supposedly we'll be getting a Grock 5.
And if you remember, Grock 4 just came
out like a month ago. So crazy that he's
already talking about Gro 5. Also, we
have to keep in mind this is Elon.
Elon's not always the best with
timelines. So, if I had to guess whether
or not Grok 5 will actually see the
light of day before the end of 2025, my
guess is probably not, just based on the
track record. But, I'm hoping for it. I
love seeing new models. I love testing
new models. I'm trying to find new ways
to test new models. My goal is to figure
out some sort of benchmark of like how
is this actually useful for everyday
people instead of the crazy math and
science benchmarks we're getting now. I
want to develop my own. I haven't sort
of landed on exactly what that looks
like yet, but I love all these new AI
models coming out so that I can sort of
test them against each other. So
hopefully we do get Grock 5 by the end
of the year. I'm just not going to hold
my breath. And that's what I got for
you. I know, big week. Crazy week. So
much stuff happened. So many new
releases. GPT5, GPT OSS, Enthropic Opus
4.1, Genie 3, 11 Labs Music, new models
in Leonardo, new Quinn image models. It
has been a week, a crazy week, a fun
week. If you're paying attention to AI,
this has been one of the best weeks
ever. So much good stuff and it just
feels like it's accelerating even more.
And as you know, I'm here for it. So, if
you want to stay looped in on the latest
AI news and get tutorials on how to use
all of the latest cool AI stuff that
comes out, make sure you like this
video, subscribe to this channel, and I
will make sure more cool stuff shows up
in your YouTube feed all about the
latest cool technology that you can play
with right now. But that's what I got
for you for this one. Thank you so much
for hanging out with me and nerding out
with me. Amazing week. Hopefully we get
more exciting weeks like this this year
and I'm here for it. Hopefully you'll
join me for future episodes like this.
And uh yeah, that's all I got for you.
Thanks for nerding out and hopefully
I'll see you in the next one. Bye-bye.
Thank you so much for nerding out with
me today. If you like videos like this,
make sure to give it a thumbs up and
subscribe to this channel. I'll make
sure more videos like this show up in
your YouTube feed. And if you haven't
already, check out futuretools.io io
where I share all the coolest AI tools
and all the latest AI news. And there's
an awesome free newsletter. Thanks
again. Really appreciate you.